avirtualexit.com 2011-06-01

# Privacy Policy

Since launching A Virtual Exit i recognized that individuals who visit my website value their privacy. However, due to the collaborative and social nature of the blogsphere, i do collect some private information when you interact with this web site. This privacy statement is aimed to explains what personal information i collect and use this information.

### General Guidelines

  * No registration of any kind is required in order to interact with this website. 
  * If you leave a comment on one of my posts, your email address will be stored in my database. That data is kept over at my hosting server in the USA. Security measures were implemented in order to safeguard your email address details.
  * I use a few web site performance tracking system including (but not limited to): Google Analytics, 103Bees, HitTail, AwStats etc’. Most of those applications do not identify your personal data, however, they identify several properties of your system such as IP Address, Operating System version, Browser type, Geographical Region etc’. I reserve the right to use that information in order to optimize technical and marketing aspects of this web site. An exception to the above statement are services like MyBlogLog, a blog tracking system that allows additional tracking options, such as identify links you clicked on etc’. I have no interest in that information and i won’t keep it on my servers. Look at the [MyBlogLog privacy statement](http://www.mybloglog.com/buzz/privacy/) for more details. 
  * Like the great majority of the Internet sites, we place Cookies in your PC.Cookies are small packets of data stored on your computer. We place those packets on your computer so we can then recognize the computer when you revisit this web site. Cookies effectively enable sites to better customize the site to your needs and interests, so that it can be as valuable to you as possible. You are free to delete our cookie when you see fit.
  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 
  * If you are under 16 years old- please do not interact with this website. No part of this website is constructed to attract individuals under 16. 

### Comment Policy

  * All comments are moderated. I reserve the right not to publish your comment at my sole discretion
  * When making comments try to be tolerant and don’t make a statement that might offend other readers. 
  * Linking to gambling, adult, pharmacy web sites is strictly prohibited. Same goes for web sites that promote violence and racism of any kind
  * Use of affiliate links in comments is prohibited
  * I reserve the right to contact you via email regarding a comment you made in this web site
